<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="navigation_options">
        <item>Menu</item>
        <item>contact</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="site_navigation_options">
        <item>Nav...</item>
        <item>Menu</item>
        <item>Contact</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
    </string-array>
    <color name="background_gradient_end">#D32F2F</color>
    <color name="background_gradient_start">#B71C1C</color>
    <color name="button_text">#FFFFFF</color>
    <color name="card_background">#FFFFFF</color>
    <color name="dark_red">#B71C1C</color>
    <color name="light_brown">#D2B48C</color>
    <color name="light_brown_border">#A0896B</color>
    <color name="light_brown_darker">#B8A082</color>
    <color name="light_brown_lighter">#DCC0A0</color>
    <color name="light_gray">#DDDDDD</color>
    <color name="medium_gray">#555555</color>
    <color name="primary_red">#D32F2F</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>
    <string name="about_content">
        We are dedicated to bringing you the best travel experiences around the world.
        Explore iconic landmarks, cultural treasures, and hidden gems with our guided tours and travel tips.\n\n
        Our mission is to make your journey unforgettable and seamless.\n\n
        Thank you for trusting us!
    </string>
    <string name="about_content1">Welcome to Ezidon Heritage Tourist!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Ezidon Heritage Tourist</string>
    <string name="btn_back_to_login">Go to Login</string>
    <string name="btn_login">Login</string>
    <string name="btn_signup">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="btn_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="btn_view">View</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="hint_address">Enter your email address</string>
    <string name="hint_email">username</string>
    <string name="hint_first">FirstName</string>
    <string name="hint_last">LastName</string>
    <string name="hint_message">Tell us more about your inquiry....</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="hint_subject">What is this regarding?</string>
    <string name="log">USER LOGIN</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_description">With open arms overlooking Rio, Christ the Redeemer is one of the most iconic statues in the world. A symbol of peace and faith, it welcomes millions of visitors to Brazil every year.</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_line1">1. Stands 30 meters tall, with arms stretching 28 meters wide.</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_line2">2. Built in 1931 after 9 years of construction</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_line3">3. Made of reinforced concrete and soapstone.</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_line4">4. Survived multiple lightning strikes over the years.</string>
    <string name="site_christ_redeemer_title">Christ the Redeemer (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil)</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_description">The Colosseum is Rome’s grand amphitheater and a window into the gladiatorial past of the Roman Empire. Built nearly 2,000 years ago, it once hosted roaring crowds, deadly battles, and spectacular shows. Today, it stands as a mighty symbol of Roman engineering and endurance.</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_line1">1. Could seat over 50,000 people.</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_line2">2. Fights sometimes included wild animals like lions and tigers.</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_line3">3. It had a retractable awning system for shade.</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_line4">4. Despite earthquakes and stone robbers, much of it still survives.</string>
    <string name="site_colosseum_title">The Colosseum (Rome, Italy)</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_description">Stretching over rugged mountains and deserts, the Great Wall of China is the longest man-made structure in the world. Built over centuries to protect against invasions, today it inspires awe with its scale and history.</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_line1">1. Extends over 21,000 km.</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_line2">2. Not visible from space with the naked eye (that’s a myth).</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_line3">3. Built by several dynasties over 2,000 years.</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_line4">4. Some parts are crumbling, others beautifully restored.</string>
    <string name="site_great_wall_title">Great Wall of China (China)</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_description">Machu Picchu, the “Lost City of the Incas,” sits high in the Andes Mountains, hidden among clouds and cliffs. Built in the 15th century and rediscovered in 1911, it remains one of the world’s greatest archaeological mysteries, a place where history and nature meet in breathtaking harmony.</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_line1">1. Constructed without mortar; the stone blocks fit together so perfectly they’ve survived centuries of earthquakes.</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_line2">2. Believed to be a royal estate of the Inca emperor Pachacuti.</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_line3">3. Over 75% of the site is original, not reconstructed.</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_line4">4. Declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1983 and one of the New Seven Wonders of the World.</string>
    <string name="site_machu_picchu_title">Machu Picchu</string>
    <string name="site_mount_description">Mount Fuji is Japan’s sacred mountain, rising gracefully with a snow-capped peak. A beloved subject of art, poetry, and pilgrimage, it’s both a natural wonder and cultural icon of Japan.</string>
    <string name="site_mount_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_mount_line1">1. Highest mountain in Japan at 3,776 meters.</string>
    <string name="site_mount_line2">2. An active volcano, though last erupted in 1707.</string>
    <string name="site_mount_line3">3. Considered one of Japan’s “Three Holy Mountains.”</string>
    <string name="site_mount_line4">4. Climbed by hundreds of thousands every summer.</string>
    <string name="site_mount_title">Mount Fuji (Japan)</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_description">The last surviving wonder of the ancient world, the Great Pyramid is a monument to the ingenuity of the ancient Egyptians. Towering above the desert sands, it has guarded the secrets of Pharaoh Khufu for over 4,500 years.</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_line1">1. Originally stood at 146 meters, the tallest man-made structure for millennia.</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_line2">2. Built with over 2 million stone blocks, each weighing tons.</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_line3">3. Aligned perfectly with the cardinal points of the compass.</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_line4">4. Nobody knows exactly how it was built — it remains a mystery.</string>
    <string name="site_pyramids_title">The Great Pyramid of Giza (Egypt)</string>
    <string name="site_statue_liberty_description">The Statue of Liberty is America’s beacon of freedom, gifted by France in 1886. She stands tall in New York Harbor, torch raised high, welcoming millions of immigrants and visitors with hope and promise.</string>
    <string name="site_statue_liberty_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_statue_liberty_title">Statue of Liberty (New York, USA)</string>
    <string name="site_statue_line1">1. The crown has 7 spikes, representing the 7 continents and 7 seas.</string>
    <string name="site_statue_line2">2. Its copper coating gives it the green color (it was once brown).</string>
    <string name="site_statue_line3">3. The statue is about 93 meters tall including the pedestal.</string>
    <string name="site_statue_line4">4. Gustave Eiffel (yes, the Eiffel Tower guy) designed the internal structure.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_line1">1. Designed by Danish architect Jørn Utzon, who won an international competition in 1957.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_line2">2. Contains over 1,000 rooms, including a concert hall with seating for 2,700.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_line3">The roof is made of over 1 million tiles imported from Sweden.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_line4">Hosts over 1,500 performances every year, attracting millions of visitors.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_opera_description">The Sydney Opera House is a dazzling architectural icon perched on Bennelong Point, Sydney Harbour. With its soaring sail-shaped shells, it is not just a performance venue, but a masterpiece of modern design and a symbol of Australia itself.</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_opera_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_sydney_opera_title">Sydney Opera House (Australia)</string>
    <string name="site_taj_line1">1. Took 22 years and about 20,000 workers to complete.</string>
    <string name="site_taj_line2">2. Changes color depending on the light (pink at dawn, golden at sunset).</string>
    <string name="site_taj_line3">3. Perfectly symmetrical except for the emperor’s tomb.</string>
    <string name="site_taj_line4">4. Declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1983.</string>
    <string name="site_taj_mahal_description">The Taj Mahal is a white marble masterpiece built by Emperor Shah Jahan in memory of his beloved wife Mumtaz Mahal. Often called the “jewel of India,” it is both a symbol of love and one of the most beautiful buildings on earth.</string>
    <string name="site_taj_mahal_fact">Amazing Fact:</string>
    <string name="site_taj_mahal_title">Taj Mahal (Agra, India)</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_description">The Eiffel Tower is the shining crown of Paris and one of the most recognized landmarks in the world. Built in 1889 for the World’s Fair by Gustave Eiffel, it stands tall at 330 meters, offering sweeping views of the “City of Light.” By day it’s a marvel of iron engineering, and by night it transforms into a sparkling beacon with its famous hourly light show. Visiting the tower isn’t just sightseeing — it’s experiencing the beating heart of Paris.</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_fact">Amazing Facts:</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_line1">It was originally meant to be dismantled after 20 years, but it became too beloved (and useful as a radio antenna) to take down.</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_line2">The Eiffel Tower can grow taller in summer by up to 15 cm because the iron expands in heat.</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_line3">Every evening, 20,000 light bulbs twinkle on it, creating its famous 5-minute sparkle show.</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_line4">Until 1930, it held the record as the tallest structure in the world.</string>
    <string name="site_tower_paris_title">Eiffel Tower (Paris, France)</string>
    <string name="tv_signup_prompt">"Don't have an account? Sign Up"</string>
    <string name="view_button">View</string>
    <string name="wel">WELCOME!!</string>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="Theme.AppCompat.Light.NoActionBar">
        <item name="android:fontFamily">serif</item>
        <item name="colorPrimary">@color/primary_red</item>
        <item name="colorPrimaryDark">@color/dark_red</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/primary_red</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Base.Theme.Ezidon" parent="Theme.Material3.DayNight.NoActionBar">
        
        
    </style>
    <style name="PrimaryButton" parent="Widget.AppCompat.Button">
        <item name="android:background">@color/primary_red</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@color/button_text</item>
        <item name="android:fontFamily">serif</item>
        <item name="android:paddingLeft">20dp</item>
        <item name="android:paddingRight">20dp</item>
    </style>
    <style name="Theme.Ezidon" parent="Base.Theme.Ezidon"/>
</resources>